Most people don't understand how deep
submarines go. Imagine we dove to the
deepest submarine. First, we'd see small
submersibles built for research or even
luxury tourism. As we go deeper, most
military submarines operate around here.
We think these subs are built for
stealth and speed. They stay relatively
close to the surface for operations.
Now, we're starting to get to deep sea
military submarines. We know rough
depths for some of these, but the exact
depths are kept secret, but we're not
even close to the deepest we can go.
diving down thousands of meters. We're
actually no longer in a submarine. We're
in a manned submersible down here. The
pressure is around 1,000 times what it
is on the surface. The deepest crude
submersible that we know about is this
one. In 2019, it went down an insane
depth of 11,000 m, reaching the deepest
part of the ocean.
>> At bottom, repeat at bottom.
>> And this vehicle had a titanium hole 3
and 1/2 in thick to withstand the
pressure. We're making a longer video
about living underwater.